I just want to say something. If it wasn't for y'all, I would really, if it wasn't for y'all,
I would really think that I ain't doing shit because the industry I'm in does not recognize me.
And to be clear, I'm speaking about the black spaces in the industry I'm in. Cause y'all know,
I don't give two dams about any of these other spaces, but the black spaces is what I'm referring
to, which is largely in part why I've realized like I need to shift out of this industry.
You know, like I don't get invited to essence women in Hollywood. I've never been invited to
the NAACP image awards. I've been, I've been nominated for an image award. Never been invited
to the NAACP image awards. Never been honored at black girls rock. Like I've hosted these events.
You know what I'm saying? Um, I literally hosted the BET awards in 2020 in my house and I was not
invited to the BET awards since. So I just want to thank y'all for always reminding me
that I really am valuable because the game and the industry that I've been in has never let me know.